[
    {
        "question": "â™–ğŸ”  *_~`ÙˆÙŠÙ„ÙŠØ§Ù…`~_*  ğŸ‘ŒğŸ˜º",
        "response": "ÙˆÙŠÙ„ÙŠØ§Ù…"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™•â˜  *_~`Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ`~_*  â™¢ğŸ­",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ©ğŸ‰  *_~`Ø§ÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ†`~_*  â™™âœŒ",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ†"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™£ğŸ‘‘  *_~`Ø§Ø³ØªØ§`~_*  â˜¯ğŸ©",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™ğŸ’š  *_~`Ù‡Ù…ØªØ§Ø±Ùˆ`~_*  ğŸ’˜ğŸ’¥",
        "response": "Ù‡Ù…ØªØ§Ø±Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸğŸ’²  *_~`Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙŠÙÙŠØ§`~_*  ğŸ§ğŸ¯",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙŠÙÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜†ğŸ¯  *_~`Ù†ÙˆÙŠÙ„`~_*  â™¤â™š",
        "response": "Ù†ÙˆÙŠÙ„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ…ğŸ¸  *_~`Ø±Ø§ÙŠÙ„ÙŠ`~_*  â™ŸğŸ‘",
        "response": "Ø±Ø§ÙŠÙ„ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‹â™¬  *_~`Ø§Ù„`~_*  àµ âœ‹",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸğŸ’€  *_~`Ù„Ø§Ùˆ`~_*  â˜®â™”",
        "response": "Ù„Ø§Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’—ğŸ«  *_~`Ù…Ø§Ø¯Ø§Ø±Ø§`~_*  ğŸŸğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù…Ø§Ø¯Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â–€â–„â–€â–„â–€â–„ *_~`ÙŠÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ`~_* â–„â–€â–„â–€â–„â–€",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™ğŸƒ  *_~`Ø§ÙŠØªØ§ØªØ´ÙŠ`~_*  â™âœŠ",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØªØ§ØªØ´ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’£ğŸ‘Œ  *_~`ØªÙˆØ¨ÙŠ`~_*  â˜œğŸ ",
        "response": "ØªÙˆØ¨ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸğŸ†  *_~`Ù†ÙˆØ¨Ø§Ø±Ø§`~_*  ğŸ’”ğŸŸ",
        "response": "Ù†ÙˆØ¨Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”  ğŸ€  *_~`Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸ€  ğŸ”",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜¢â›µ  *_~`Ù‡Ø§Ø´ÙŠØ±Ø§Ù…Ø§`~_*  â™ğŸ˜",
        "response": "Ù‡Ø§Ø´ÙŠØ±Ø§Ù…Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’ğŸ’™  *_~`Ø¨ÙˆØ±ÙˆØªÙˆ`~_*  ğŸ˜³â™•",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙˆØ±ÙˆØªÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’œğŸˆ  *_~`ÙŠÙˆØ³ÙˆØ¨`~_*  ğŸ’—ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆØ³ÙˆØ¨"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ°  ğŸ€  *_~`Ø±ÙŠÙ…`~_*  ğŸ€  ğŸ°",
        "response": "Ø±ÙŠÙ…"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜ ğŸ‘¤  *_~`Ø§ÙˆØªØ´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§ Ø´ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙŠ`~_*  â™¥â™ª",
        "response": "Ø§ÙˆØªØ´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§ Ø´ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ‹ğŸ”¥  *_~`ÙƒÙŠØ¯`~_*  ğŸˆâœ‹",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠØ¯"
    },
    {
        "question": " â–‚ â–„ â–… â–† â–‡ â–ˆ  *_~`Ù…ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø³Ø§`~_*  â–ˆ â–‡ â–† â–… â–„ â–‚",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø³Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "(ã£â—”â—¡â—”)ã£ â™¥ *_~`Ø¯Ø§Ù†Ø²Ùˆ`~_* â™¥",
        "response": "Ø¯Ø§Ù†Ø²Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â˜®ğŸ’£  *_~`ÙˆÙŠÙ†Øº`~_*  àµ ğŸ˜",
        "response": "ÙˆÙŠÙ†Øº"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‰ğŸ˜º  *_~`ØªÙŠÙ†Ø´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§Ù†`~_*  ğŸ¼ğŸŠ",
        "response": "ØªÙŠÙ†Ø´ÙŠÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
        "question": "*_~`Ø¨ÙŠÙƒÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†`~_*",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙŠÙƒÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¥ğŸ‘‘  *_~`ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸ‘®ğŸ’£",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¤â™¤  *_~`Ø¬ÙŠØ±Ø§ÙŠØ§`~_*  ğŸ‘ºâ™¦",
        "response": "Ø¬ÙŠØ±Ø§ÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‰â˜¯  *_~`ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸŠâ™•",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§Ø²ÙŠÙƒØ§Ø¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™˜ğŸ‘¤  *_~`ÙƒÙˆÙƒÙˆÙ…ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸºğŸƒ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆÙƒÙˆÙ…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥ğŸ‘»  *_~`ØºÙŠÙˆ`~_*  â™¡ğŸ’š",
        "response": "ØºÙŠÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŸâ™¥  *_~`ØªØ´ÙŠÙˆ`~_*  ğŸŸâ˜¯",
        "response": "ØªØ´ÙŠÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ”¥â™  *_~`Ø³Ø§Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸ‘£ğŸ‘¹",
        "response": "Ø³Ø§Ø³ÙˆØ±ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœ·  ğŸ€  *_~`Ù†ÙŠØ²ÙˆÙƒÙˆ`~_*  ğŸ€  âœ·",
        "response": "Ù†ÙŠØ²ÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸŒ·ğŸ‰  *_~`Ù…ÙŠØ¯ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§`~_*  ğŸ¸ğŸ‘½",
        "response": "Ù…ÙŠØ¯ÙˆØ±ÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "â™£âœŒ  *_~`Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸºğŸ’",
        "response": "Ù†ÙŠØ¬ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸºğŸ¤  *_~`Ø§Ø³ØªØ§`~_*  ğŸ¯ğŸ¨",
        "response": "Ø§Ø³ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘ğŸ†  *_~`Ù„ÙŠØ²Ø§`~_*  â™¢ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠØ²Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‘ğŸ¯  *_~`ÙƒØ§ØºÙˆÙŠØ§`~_*  ğŸ’€ğŸ£",
        "response": "ÙƒØ§ØºÙˆÙŠØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§  ğŸ€  *_~`Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§`~_*  ğŸ€  ğŸ§",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ“  ğŸ€  *_~`Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙƒØ§`~_*  ğŸ€  ğŸ“",
        "response": "Ø§Ù„ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ä±llÄ±llÄ±   ğŸ€  *_~`Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ§`~_*  ğŸ€   Ä±llÄ±llÄ±",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤ğŸ¬  *_~`Ø²ÙŠÙ†ØªØ³Ùˆ`~_*  ğŸ’¢ğŸª",
        "response": "Ø²ÙŠÙ†ØªØ³Ùˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘»ğŸ“  *_~`Ø±ÙŠÙ†ØºÙˆÙƒÙˆ`~_*  ğŸ§ğŸ”¥",
        "response": "Ø±ÙŠÙ†ØºÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’ğŸ’²  *_~`Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ`~_*  â˜†ğŸ’—",
        "response": "Ù„ÙŠÙØ§ÙŠ"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’¢â˜Ÿ  *_~`ÙƒÙˆØ±ØªØ§`~_*  ğŸˆğŸ’£",
        "response": "ÙƒÙˆØ±ØªØ§"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ˜ˆğŸˆ  *_~`Ù‡ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙƒØ§`~_*  ğŸ’™ğŸƒ",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠØ³ÙˆÙƒØ§"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ’â™˜  *_~`Ø§Ù†ÙˆØ³`~_*  ğŸ˜ğŸ‘‘",
        "response": "Ø§Ù†ÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜ŸğŸˆ  *_~`Ø¨ÙŠØ§ÙƒÙˆØºØ§Ù†`~_*  ğŸ’â™§",
        "response": "Ø¨ÙŠØ§ÙƒÙˆØºØ§Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "ã€ï½¡_ï½¡ã€‘ *_~`Ø´ÙˆÙƒÙˆ`~_* ã€ï½¡_ï½¡ã€‘",
        "response": "Ø´ÙˆÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸğŸ§  *_~`Ø¯ÙŠÙƒÙˆ`~_*  ğŸ„âœŠ",
        "response": "Ø¯ÙŠÙƒÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "â–‘â–’â–“â–ˆ *_~`ÙŠØ§Ù…ÙŠ`~_* â–ˆâ–“â–’â–‘",
        "response": "ÙŠØ§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ†ğŸ‘  *_~`ÙØ§Ù†Ø¬Ø§Ù†Ø³`~_*  ğŸ®ğŸ…",
        "response": "ÙØ§Ù†Ø¬Ø§Ù†Ø³"
    },
    {
       "question": "â˜®ğŸ¤  *_~`ÙŠÙˆÙ„ÙŠÙˆØ³`~_*  ğŸœâ™œ",
        "response": "ÙŠÙˆÙ„ÙŠÙˆØ³"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘ŠâœŠ  *_~`ØªØ³ÙˆÙ…ÙˆØºÙˆ`~_*  ğŸ£ğŸ¨",
        "response": "ØªØ³ÙˆÙ…ÙˆØºÙˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘»ğŸ’›  *_~`Ù†Ø§Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ`~_*  ğŸƒğŸ’›",
        "response": "Ù†Ø§Ù†Ø§Ù…ÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ ğŸ  *_~`Ø§ÙŠØ²Ù†`~_*  â™—â™š",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠØ²Ù†"   
    },
    {
       "question": "â™”ğŸ’  *_~`Ø²Ø§Ø±Ø§ÙƒÙŠ`~_*  âœŒâ˜†",
        "response": "Ø²Ø§Ø±Ø§ÙƒÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ»ğŸ’œ  *_~`Ø§ÙˆØ±Ø§Ù‡Ø§Ø±Ø§`~_*  â˜¹ğŸº",
        "response": "Ø§ÙˆØ±Ø§Ù‡Ø§Ø±Ø§"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ©ğŸª  *_~`Ø§ÙŠÙ†ÙˆÙŠ`~_*  â˜¹ğŸ‘¹",
        "response": "Ø§ÙŠÙ†ÙˆÙŠ"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ‘½ğŸ‰  *_~`ØºÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†`~_*  ğŸ²â™",
        "response": "ØºÙˆÙ‡Ø§Ù†"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ²â™•  *_~`ÙƒÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ„ÙŠÙ†`~_*  ğŸ˜²ğŸŠ",
        "response": "ÙƒÙŠØ±ÙŠÙ„ÙŠÙ†"
    },
    {
       "question": "*â€¢.Â¸â™¡ *_~`Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ³ÙˆØ±Ùˆ`~_* â™¡Â¸.â€¢*",
        "response": "Ù‡ÙŠÙ†Ø§ØªØ³ÙˆØ±Ùˆ"
    },
    {
       "question": "-æ¼«~*'Â¨Â¯Â¨'*Â·èˆ~ *_~`Ø±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠÙ„`~_* ~èˆ*'Â¨Â¯Â¨'*Â·~æ¼«-",
       "response": "Ø±ÙŠØªØ´ÙŠÙ„"
}
]
